.
# We can laugh ha-ha
We can sing la-la-la-la
# We can make anything
# Hold my hand
# Make a magical land
# When letters get together
we go alakazam
# We can run, we can slide
We can hide in a box
# Are you ready for some fun
with the Alphablocks?
# Alphablocks! #
G, G, G, G.
I'm growing my hair for the party.
Oooh, it's lovely and long!
Ready, everyone? It's party time...
But whose party is it? I know!
Let's find out... IR,
IR-IR-IRIR.
G. IR.
L. Girl!
Hello! ALL: Hello, Girl.
We're having a party.
A party? I love parties.
Whose party is it? Yours!
A party for me!
But I want lots and lots
and lots of friends for my party.
SHE WHISTLES
Ha-ha, hiya!
No, I mean lots and lots and lots
more than that.
SHE WHISTLES MORE LOUDLY
Aaaah! A!
That's better.
Everybody, hold hands.
BIRTHDAY!
It's your birthday party.
Happy birthday!
Yay!
First, we need to make
a birthday cake!
Yummy! We need eggs, flour,
sugar and butter...
(and a pinch of fairy dust.)
Then you stir it all up.
STIR!
Stir! Stir! Stir!
SHE GIGGLES
Sticky, messy fun!
Now for the best bit.
SHE WHISTLES
QU! We need to decorate my birthday
cake.
Everybody, hold hands.
SQUIRT!
Squirt! Squirt! Squirt!
Squirt! Squirt! Squirt! Squirt!
A squidgy, squirty mess!
SHE GIGGLES
Sticky-yuck-yuck. Ha, ha!
I need some new birthday clothes!
SKIRT!
I love my new skirt.
Now it's time for...
party games!
We need music. Band!
Let's play musical statues.
W-What do we have to do?
I'll show you.
When the music plays, you
have to move about like this.
Tra-la-la-la-la...
When it stops, you freeze.
Well done. Ready, everyone?
MUSIC PLAYS
Freeze!
TWIRL!
EVERYONE LAUGHS
Ooooh! I said freeze.
It's time for birthday presents.
Eh?!
Have we got a present? Ah!
This is a special cake,
birthday girl.
When you blow out the candles,
you can make a wish. A wish!
# Happy birthday,
happy birthday Girl
# You can wish for anything
in the world. #
I wish... I wish...
SHE TAKES A DEEP BREATH
Phooooo!
Open your eyes, birthday girl. Ha!
BIRD!
TWEETING
A bird! I'm flying on a bird!
I love birds.
Oooh, this is the best birthday ever!
SHE LAUGHS
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd