QUACK!
# Sarah and Duck
# Sarah and Duck. #
QUACK!
This morning, Sarah and Duck are reading the newspaper.
Well, at least Sarah is.
Ooh!
Ooh. You dropped something there.
QUACK!
Oh!
What are they?
Seeds.
They sound...small.
Why not plant them and see what grows?
OK. Come on, Duck.
Is it not better to grow them in the back garden?
No. We will see them more here.
Quite right. Carry on.
Here?
Duck seems to approve.
QUACK!
Thank you, Duck.
Not wasting any time, are you?
No.
DUCK QUACKS
Take a seed, Duck.
QUACK!
One, two, three.
Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye.
QUACK! QUACK!
Finished.
Job well done.
Oh. Ugh.
Well, you are covered, Sarah.
QUACK!
You too, Duck!
Ugh. Muddy Duck.
Come on, let's clean up.
DUCK QUACKS
QUACK! QUACK!
Aren't ducks supposed to like water?
SHE GIGGLES
Anything happening yet?
No, not yet.
Oh, dear. How about some dinner?
OK.
So, what else are you doing today?
Waiting.
Oh?
For the seeds to grow.
You know it could take a while.
That's OK.
THEY YAWN
SHE SIGHS
Oh, dear. Perhaps if you go to bed, it might happen faster.
Morning, Sarah.
Morning.
- Hello.
- Hello!
- Ahoy!
Ooh. Hello.
They must be onions, though they don't look quite big enough.
They're onion children!
Mmm. Maybe they still need a little bit longer to grow.
Well, we can help them grow.
Great idea. How are you going to do that?
Teach them things.
Hmm. Need to warm up first.
Come on.
- ONIONS:
- Hup, hup, hup!
Rolly...over.
ONIONS CHEER
QUACK!
- ONIONS:
- Hup, hup, hup!
QUACK!
Duck...jump!
- ONIONS:
- Hey! Ho! Hup!
DUCK QUACKS
Ooh, your vegetable book.
Root vege-tables grow from their roots
all the way up out of the ground.
Here are some root vege-tables.
Carrot?
- ONIONS:
- Yes!
Turnip?
- ONIONS:
- Turnip!
Marrow.
- ONIONS:
- No, no! Ew!
Turnip!
OK, now draw your favourites.
Hmm!
- Turnip!
- Quack!
Not a bad likeness!
QUACK!
Looks like Professor Duck has some teaching to do.
Maybe some flying lessons?
QUACK!
- ONIONS:
- Ooh! Ah!
There you go, everything you need.
QUACK!
- ONIONS:
- Turnip! Turnip! Turnip!
QUACK!
- Oops!
- SHE GASPS
Shh!
THEY LAUGH
Oh, look at the book! Those vegetables seem familiar.
They're shallots.
"Shallots are like baby onions and won't grow any bigger."
They're meant to be small!
- SHALLOTS:
- Yep!
Easy mistake to make.
Besides, you shallots may have learned a thing or two.
- Thank you.
Cheers!
That's OK.
- SHALLOTS:
- Drums, drums!
- Hup, hup, hup!
- SHALLOTS:
- Thank you!
Thank you!
QUACK! QUACK! QUACK!
QUACK!
- SHALLOTS:
- Cheers!
Hooray! Well done.
# Sarah and Duck
QUACK!
# Sarah and Duck. #